<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Places of Unity</title>
    <link>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Places of Unity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place5/</guid>
      <description>This place was created in a public park behind the town hall of Bad Godesberg as part of a crystal workshop. It is closely connected to the network of trees and supports them in their work to create a harmonious and healing energy in the park and for the whole environment together with the nature beings. In this process the place is supported by the starlight from Venus. This light stimulates a natural energy flow of love (prema) and peace (shanti) in us and in the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place4/</guid>
      <description>Place of unity on Linda‘s property
This place is supported by the light of the Archangel Michael. Standing in front of it you can leave everything behind, that doesn´t belong to your true self. You can recharge your batteries and maybe you get an angel message. In the center there is a rose quartz rough, with an amethyst rough.
Four Arkansas Pts are set in each direction and connect with the 4 elements earth, air, fire and water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place3/</guid>
      <description>Place of unity and the Pleiades
You find this place in nature, in the Malibu Creek State Park in the Santa Monica Mountains. This place has a strong connection to the starlight system of the Pleiades. Here the Native Americans used to celebrate the Pleiades because of their wisdom of unity and here I had the vision of creating places of unity by myself. If you connect to the light of the Pleiades at this place, you can feel unity in your heart chakra especially if you are standing near the tree, where the energy of unity is anchored in the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place2/</guid>
      <description>The second place of unity was created in the garden of my mother. Her garden already is a wonderful place. Due to the caring love of my mother the nature beings enjoy living there. Having set the place of unity we could feel a deep and peaceful connection to the energy structures in the Earth, the leylines and a remarkable increase of power in the root chakra. Besides the place is a gift for my mother and for all the beings who come to stay in the beautiful garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://places-of-unity.com/portfolio/place1/</guid>
      <description>The first place of unity wasn´t planned and was spontaneously created during a workshop. We just wanted to make the “fire that turns hatred into love”, but during the ritual the power of heaven and earth connected with the Christ light and this energy could be anchored in a stone that I found on the ground. It was magic!
Created at a public place this place of unity has changed its appearance over time, but it has kept its energy and offers it to the earth and all the people who come to visit this special place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>